Taine Jarvis

220 Woolwich Road London SE77QU 07432525034 taine.jarvis@gmail.com

Profile

An enthusiastic and level headed person with 3 years of experience in Building Services Engineering. Is very well rounded in all aspects of engineering and stays calm under pressure being able to handle all situations that may arise.

Works well in a team environment and is very social. Interested and passionate about engineering and is always looking for opportunities to learn new skills.

Key Skills

- Good organisational skills
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- Communication skills
- DipHE in Building Engineering
- Ability to self-manage and organise own workload

Employment history

CBRE | General Maintenance Operative | September 2022 – December 2023

Fabric duties such as painting, fixing doors, hinges, locks, and basic plumbing. Communicating effectively with clients and setting manageable expectations. Ensuring works are completed safely as per RAMS guidelines.

BGIS | Multi Skiled Engineer | April 2022 - September 2022

Working in various CBRE sites across the city of London. Ensuring compliance with Health and Safety requirements. Undertaking tests and maintenance of a variety of instrumentation & control systems sensors and performing planned preventative and reactive maintenance on all associated Operations of building services e.g. AHUs, access controls, light fittings and Emergency Light Testing.

Heritage Hotel | Maintenance Engineer | December 2019 - April 2022

Working alongside senior engineers as part of a team. Performing inspections

of mechanical and electrical equipment and systems to ensure they are safe and efficient in accordance with agreed procedures and company policy standards. Provide technical incident reports where requested and provide supporting documentation of incidents. Assisting senior engineers on any callouts in the building and updating any existing records to show that equipment fulfils compliance guidelines.

JDK Maintenance | Building Services Engineer | January 2019 - December 2019

Ensuring compliance with Health and Safety requirements and assisting in any training of the team. Undertaking tests and maintenance of a variety of instrumentation & control systems sensors and performing planned preventative and reactive maintenance on all associated Operations of building services e.g. AHUs access controls and light fittings and Emergency Lighting Testing. Performing Inspections of Mechanical and Electrical equipment and systems to ensure it's safe and efficient in accordance with agreed procedures and company policy standards. Provide technical incident reports where requested and provide supporting documentation of incidents.

Qualifications

January 2018 - December 2018 | Auckland University of Technology | DipHE Building Engineering

- DipHE Building Engineering
- Awarded the Maori Leadership Scholarship for showing leadership qualities in extra curricular activities

Keys Skills: I have a good understanding of Building Services Engineering. I have an understanding of Software Engineering languages such as HTML, CSS, and Javascript. CSCS card holder.

<u>Interests</u>

I enjoy socialising, meeting new people, playing rugby, spending time with family and reading new books.

References available upon request